https://www.thomasneches.com/privacypolicy.htm

Toggle navigation
About Us Our FirmThomas M. NechesYael IromShari YarosPublicationsPublic SpeakingReferencesMCLE CoursesCourse TopicsRecent MCLE CoursesPrivacy PolicyCPA Expert Witness Services Business ValuationFraudIntellectual PropertyLost ProfitsWage and Hour Class ActionWrongful TerminationRepresentative Engagements AntitrustBreach of ContractBusiness ValuationEntertainment IndustryFraudIntellectual PropertyLender LiabilityPersonal Injury and Wrongful DeathReal PropertySecurities FraudStatistical and Computer DatabaseWrongful TerminationWage Hour Class ActionTrial TestimonyContact Us
About Us Privacy PolicyHomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy NoticeAccountants who provide professional services involving financial matters of clients may now be required by federal law to inform their clients of their policies regarding the privacy of client information.
The purpose of this notice is to explain what we will be doing with the financial information you provide to us and the ways we will protect your privacy. Types of Nonpublic Personal Information We CollectWe collect nonpublic personal information about you provided to us by you or obtained by us in the course of providing you with services you have requested.
This information, in some cases, includes information about your personal finances and property. Disclosure of InformationWe disclose nonpublic personal information about you only to individuals or entities necessary to provide you the services you have requested.
In particular, our staff may have access to your nonpublic personal information.
In some situations we may provide information to another organization (for example, your accountant, your realtor, or insurance company) to obtain information or assist in providing the services you have requested. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except as is necessary to provide you with the services you have requested. You Have The Right to Prohibit DisclosureIf for any reason you do not want us to provide nonpublic personal information about you to other parties in the course of providing you the services you requested, you may direct us not to make those disclosures.
If you wish to direct us not to disclose information, please call Thomas Neches at (213) 624-8150. Your Privacy Is Important to UsWe retain records and files relating to the professional services you have asked us to provide.
To guard your nonpublic personal information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards on this information.
Feel free to call us with any questions you may have about protecting your privacy.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS, PLEASE CALL THOMAS NECHES DIRECTLY AT 213.624.8150.CONTACT
US2020 Copyright Thomas Neches & Company LLP. All rights reserved.  |
Home
About Us
Representative Engagements
Trial Testimony
Privacy
Contact Us
Sitemap
Thomas Neches & Company LLP | 633 West 5th Street, Suite 2800 | Los Angeles, California 90071-2039 | Phone: (213) 624-8150 | Fax: (213) 223-2304 | Email: tmn@thomasneches.com
Website Design by LADezign
